Alberto Scotti

Digital Media Student

A creative and engaging technological student who is curios of the late technology to create VFX Short Movies and 3D Animations. I was born in Italy but raised in France at a young age, and with Italian parents I became bilingual in French and Italian. I then moved to Singapore for 2 years and followed my studies in French and started to study Mandarin. Finally I moved to Hong-Kong for 3 year and finish my high-school to then move to the UK (Leeds) for the BA Digital Media and finally to London to study Visual Effects at Escape Studios.

me18asd@leeds.ac.uk

London, United Kingdom

alberto5755.github.io

in linkedin.com/in/alberto-scotti

EDUCATION

BA Digital Media

University of Leeds

09/2018 - 05/2021

Relevant Modules

- Design for Digital Media
- 2D Animation
- Interface Design
- Dynamic Web Programming

Leeds, UK

- Digital Storytelling
- Motion Graphics
- Working in digital media teams

High School

French International School of Hong Kong

09/2015 - 05/2018

Hong Kong

Certificate

- French Baccalaureate (average mark of 13.5/20)
- Scientific pathway

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship at 8be

06/2020 - 07/2020

Rome, Italy

8be is an agency that provides consulting, web development and production services **Achievements**

- Generating creative ideas for productions such as movies and adverts
- Adapting creative projects according to critics to target specific goals and audiences

Internship at Knorr-Bremnse HQ

02/2015 - 03/2015

Knorr-Bremse is a company that produces braking systems for road and rail vehicles

Achievements

- Increased confidence in professional communication and teamworking
- Initation to the awareness of the company's organization through different sectors such as R&D and Communication-Marketing

SKILLS

Adobe Suite				0
Blender			0	0
Maya		0	0	0
Substance Painter		0	0	0
Unity		0	0	0
Houdini	0	0	0	0

PROJECTS

Compositing Cybernetic Hand

3/2021 - 6/2021

- Tracking of footage in order to apply the motion to the model
- Cleanup with Content-Aware and Chroma Keying of the green props
- Compositing of rendered images with color adjustement layers

Cybernetic Hand Model

12/2020 - 2/2021

- Learned the tools of hard surface modelling (boleans and extrusions)
- Texturing of the model procedurally with noise textures
- · Rigged the hand through bones and contraints

Car animation

09/2020 - 10/2020

- Rigged a car with scripted drivers
- Animated the car motion along path constraint
- Parented various camera angles for creative angles

Animation and Storytelling

03/2019 - 11/2019

- Advanced Work with Adobe After Effects
- Expressed a story through a keyframed animation
- Understanded the workflow of 2.5D animations

Augmented Reality App

10/2019 - 1/2020

- Worked with Unity, Blender and Xcode (for iOS compatibility)
- Expressed creativity through 3D graphics working with AR
- Created a colosseum model on Blender and the app through Unity

LANGUAGES



INTERESTS

